Holly Wilkalis

Email:
holly.wilkalis@gmail.com
Phone:
503.267.1698

Github:
/hollywilkalis
LinkedIn:
/holly-wilkalis

SUMMARY

Junior web developer with close to a decade of experience improving processes and solving problems with technology. Currently studying React, Javascript, HTML and CSS in my quest to make web user interfaces everywhere more accessible and user-friendly.

SKILLS

- Javascript
- ¡Query
- React
- · Angular2

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Pair programming

- GitHub
- Adobe Creative Suite: InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver

PROJECTS

Oregon WIC Photo Library

This is a custom photo library built with React and Javascript (project in progress).

Github repository: http://bit.ly/2t4xftQ

Cider taproom

This is a demonstration project working in React for the first time.

Github repository: http://bit.ly/2CMbWgc

EDUCATION

Epicodus Code School - Studying web development, specializing in React, Javascript, Angular2, HTML, and CSS

Portland State University - Bachelor of Science, Community Development

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Coordinator, BSI EHS Services and Solutions - 2017

- Begin developing processes for management and tracking of marketing assets (trade show booths, materials, promotional items).
- Coordinate company's LinkedIn and Twitter accounts.
- Manage promotion and logistics for webinars and other training events.
- Create content for websites and e-mail campaigns using HTML, Vertical Response, and Pardot.

EXPERIENCE (continued)

Web Content Migration Analyst (limited duration), Oregon Health Authority - 2016-2017

- Assist team with migration project moving a large site with more than 2000 pages and hundreds
 of large asset libraries to a new version of Sharepoint.
- Create new sub-site navigation and page layouts for existing site content using mobile-optimized templates.
- Contribute to and apply style guides and process documentation to maintain coherent information architecture and interaction design patterns.
- Identify, document and resolve issues with new site platform.
- Identify ways to improve site organization and presentation using newly available content management tools, and work with migration team to implement solutions.
- Develop training and competency standards for web editors.

Operations & Policy Analyst, Oregon WIC Program - 2009-2016

- Write, design and edit program materials including outreach brochures, forms, annual report, and participant education materials.
- Create and manage content for large web site and review work of other web editors.
- Manage Facebook and Twitter accounts in collaboration with other social media team members.
- Provide technical support for online staff training modules.
- Serve on departmental Web Council to advise on web policy and procedures.

Administrative Coordinator, HOST Development - 2006-2009

 Managed office operations for small nonprofit housing developer, including accounts payable and sales support.

Program Coordinator, Oregon Hunger Relief Task Force - 1998-2006

- Coordinated a child nutrition outreach project that resulted in a 40% increase in participation in the program in the targeted areas.
- Hired and supervised a series of AmeriCorps*VISTA members.
- Developed funding proposals, advised on project budgets, and wrote grant applications and reports.

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Portland Old Time Music Gathering

- Box office manager, 2015 present
- Volunteer coordinator, 2017 present

Hands On Greater Portland

Volunteer leader, 2007 - present